You said
you'd marry Joey?
You have to realize
I was exhausted
I was emotional...
I would have said yes
to anybody.
Like the time
when you and I got married.
I'm not helping.
So you said
yes to him
and you just had
our baby.
That is right.
And traditionally,
the daddy is supposed
to give the mommy a present
but I am prepared
to let that go.
So when I came in here
to see if you wanted to maybe
start things up again
you were engaged
to my best friend.
Well... really?
I thought Chandler
was your best friend.
Chandler's my oldest friend.
Joey's more... No. uh-uh-uh!
Hey, guys, I'm
gonna take off.
I just wanted
to say good-bye.
Rachel said she'd marry you?
This isn't the right room.
Sorry, folks.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, I don't
want to be negative
so I'll say that most
of the signs you bought
are good.
No, they ran out
of "It's a girl."
But I can fix this one.
You see?
Mm-hmm.
So sexy.
Honey?
Yeah?
Honey, why don't you go
lie down?
No, no, it's okay-- Ross
and Rachel will be back soon
and then I got to go
to the office.
Am I producing them?
Why are you so tired?
I couldn't sleep last night.
And then I start worrying
about this big divisional
meeting I have later today.
The more I worried about it,
the more I couldn't sleep.
You know, I was like
"If I fall asleep now,
I'll get six hours' sleep."
Then, "If I fall asleep now,
I'll get five hours' sleep."
No matter what I did,
I couldn't fall asleep.
You know what
you should have done?
You should have told yourself
that little story.
Hi.
Welcome home.
Phoebe did the signs.
RACHEL:
Oh, you guys.
Thanks for
doing this.
Look at all stuff
people sent.
Ohh... ah!
Oh, my gosh. Look, there's
something every mother needs.
A giant stuffed gorilla
that takes up
the entire apartment.
What are people think...
Oh, you guys, I love it.
And so, where's Ross?
He's downstairs
getting the stuff
out of the cab.
Uh, is he still mad at us?
Well, you more than me.
But he can't stay too mad at me.
I mean, I just had his baby.
That's not fair.
I can't do that.
Yeah, and I'm not so sure you
should be here when he comes up.
See, this is
what I was afraid of.
I didn't think
I should be here either
but somebody said
he'd be over it by now.
Hey, what do I know?
I wanted to get
a bigger gorilla.
The numbers
we're seeing
in Chicago, New York
and London
are consistently solid
but many of our
field offices
have reported
disappointing yields.
Boston is down,
Atlanta is down
Houston is down--
I could go on and on
but instead
of boring you
I'll go straight
to my 42-point plan.
Walter.
PHOEBE:
She's just so cute.
Oh, I just want
to bite her ear off
and use it
as a sucking candy.
Phoebe!
But I could take one
of those little feet
and put it
in a pita pocket.
Okay, I put most
of the stuff away.
Oh, great. The pacifiers?
Uh, it's in
the cupboard.
The burping cloths?
Uh, linen closet.
The diapers?
In the hospital.
You guys got
a hospital? Fancy.
Well, I, uh, left
the diapers at
the hospital.
There's some in the
bag, but I'll run out
and get some more.
All right, thanks.
Could you stop at the coffee
house and get me a muffin?
Oh, sure. What kind?
Uh, let me think.
What do I want?
Please, take your time.
It's an important decision.
Not like, say, I don't know,
deciding to marry someone.
This is about a muffin.
Blueberry.
Blueberry it is.
Thank you.
Wow, he's really not
letting this go, is he?
How long do you think
that's going to last?
Well, I don't know--
he got over
the "we were on a break" thing
really quickly.
You know, I can't even
worry about it right now.
'Cause I've got
the cutie little baby.
Oh, I can't believe
how much I love her.
I mean, I can't get enough
of her.
Like, right now, I miss her.
I actually miss her.
You know, that's... that's her.
Oh, God, look
at her sleeping.
Oh, I love you so much.
I think I'm going
to wake her up.
No, no, Rach. You know,
you're never supposed
to wake a sleeping baby.
I can do whatever I want.
I made her.
Come on, little
girl, oh, yes.
Hello, Emma, hi.
( Emma crying )
Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I would say "I told you so"
but she's kind of doing that
for me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Mommy's so sorry.
Go back to sleep...
shh-shh-shh.
Go back to sleep.
It really breaks
your heart, doesn't it?
It really does.
How long do you think
we have to stay?
Okay, if everyone's on board,
it's settled. Chandler!
Chandler!
Yeah?
Are you
on board?
Yes.
Then problem solved.
Chandler will be running
our office in Tulsa.
You're going
to love Oklahoma.
( Emma crying )
All right,
we already tried
feeding her,
changing her,
burping her...
Oh, try this one.
Go back in time
and listen to Phoebe.
All right, here's something.
It says to try holding the baby
close to your body
and then swing her rapidly
from side to side.
Okay.
( crying stops )
It worked.
Oh... no... just stopped
to throw up a little bit.
Oh, what am I going to do?
It's been hours
and it won't stop crying.
Uh, "she," Rach.
Not "it"-- "she."
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
God, I'm losing
my mind.
Yeah, no kidding.
This just proves
no good can come
from having sex with Ross!
Hey, Gunther,
could I get a couple of
blueberry muffins to go?
Diapers, huh?
Yep.
So I guess Rachel
had your baby.
Yep. Can you believe it?
Nope.
I can't even believe she slept
with you in the first place.
Huh?
Oh, oh, you mean like, uh...
Hey.
Your muffins.
Ross, I know
you're pissed at me
but we have to talk
about this.
Uh, actually, uh,
we don't.
Fine, okay, fine,
but I got to say
technically, I didn't
even do anything wrong.
What? You didn't
do anything wrong?
I-I said I didn't technically.
Well, let's put aside
the fact that you
"accidentally" picked up
my grandmother's ring
and you "accidentally"
proposed to Rachel...
Can I just stop you
right there for a second?
When people do this...
I don't really know
what that means.
You were saying?
And I can even
understand that you
couldn't tell Rachel
but why couldn't
you tell me, huh?
You had all day to,
and you didn't.
I know. I should have.
I'm "sorry."
Not using it right, Joe.
I'm going to go.
No. Come on, look, Ross.
We have to get past this.
Give me the bag.
No. I don't know
what else to do.
I said I'm sorry.
Joey...
Now you should
scream at me
or curse me or hit me.
I'm not going
to hit you.
Why not?
You'll feel better.
I'll feel better.
And you know
you want to.
I can see it in your eyes.
No, I don't.
A little bit.
No.
A little bit more.
Give me the bag.
No, hit me.
Hit me.
Joey, give me the bag.
Hit me. Hit me.
Joe, I'm not kidding.
Hit me! Hit me! Hit me!
You ducked!
I'm sorry. It was a reflex.
Oh, my God!
This really hurts!
I couldn't help it.
When a fist comes
at your face, you duck.
Look.
What is the matter with you?!
You were supposed to duck.
Why didn't you duck?
Why don't we talk about this
on the way to the hospital.
Good, good, yeah.
Maybe while we're there,
they can check your reflexes.
"Oops."
( Emma crying )
Try feeding her again.
I already fed her.
I know.
That's why I said "again."
You guys, we can't turn
on each other, okay?
That's just what she wants.
Hi.
MONICA:
Hey.
Monica, can I talk
to you outside
for a minute?
Oh, no, you guys
just stay here.
I'm going to go
check her diaper.
Pheebs, you want to come?
Oh, I'm kind of
part of this.
Actually, Pheebs
it's more of a husband and wife
kind of thing.
I knew I should have
married Chandler.
Okay, what's up?
Okay, um...
You know how we always
said it would be fun
to move to Paris
for a year?
You could study
French cooking
and I could write,
and we could picnic
along the Seine
and go wine tasting
in Bordeaux?
Oh, yes.
Okay, you know how
people say that Tulsa...
is the Paris of Oklahoma?
What? Who says that?
People who have
never been to Paris.
Wh-What's going on?
We're moving to Tulsa.
Excuse me?
Okay, Ms. McKenna
she kind of, uh,
works above my boss.
She asked me
to move to Tulsa
and be the president
of our office there
and I was sleeping and
apparently said yes.
Tulsa, Oklahoma?!
The Sooner state.
Whatever that is.
Chandler, I don't even want
to see the musical Oklahoma!
Really? "Oh, What
a Beautiful Morning"?
"Surrey With
The Fringe On Top"?
Are you trying to tell me
that we're moving to Oklahoma
or that you're gay?
Not that this matters
but did they at least
offer you a huge raise?
No, no.
But they are going to
lease us a Ford Focus.
I'll get out of it.
Thank you.
( Emma crying )
What is wrong with Emma?
Oh, she misunderstood.
She thought she
was moving to Tulsa.
Ma'am, do you
have a minute?
I kind of have some bad news.
I don't think
I can move to Tulsa.
What?
Uh, it's a funny story,
actually.
( clears throat )
Uh, I kind of fell asleep
in the meeting this morning.
So when I said
I'd move to Tulsa
I didn't really know
what I was saying.
You fell asleep?
But only because
I was up all night
worried about this meeting.
Isn't that funny?
Irony. Not a fan?
All right.
See, here's the thing.
I went home and told my wife
about Tulsa, a-and she won't go.
See, me? I love Tulsa.
Tulsa is heaven.
Tulsa is Italy.
Please don't make me go there.
Chandler, I...
No, now, now
look, Carol...
Can I call you Carol?
Why would I
when your name is Elaine?
Oh, what a great picture
of your son. Strapping!
That's a picture
of your daughter, isn't it?
Well, she's lovely.
I-I like a girl
with a strong jaw.
I'll call you from Tulsa.
Hey. So, uh, how is it?
I broke my thumb.
Your thumb?
That's weird.
Are you sure you're
punching right?
Make a fist.
Maybe later.
Ross, I feel terrible.
You know what, you can go.
I just have
to fill out some forms.
You, uh, y-you want me
to help you with that?
Why, does it look
like I'm having trouble
with my misshapen claw?
"Name."
I know "Ross," but
what's it short for?
You know, like, Rossell.
Or Rosstopher.
Just Ross.
Oh.
It's pretty.
Okay, "Date of birth."
You know my birthday.
Sure.
May...
tember?
October 18th.
"Occupation."
Dinosaurs.
Actually, I'm a paleo...
Dinosaurs is fine.
The drawing is not.
All right, uh,
w-who do you want as
your emergency contact?
Uh, Rachel, I guess.
Okay. "Relationship"?
Whoo, boy, this
could take a while.
Just, uh...
just put "roommate."
Come on.
You guys are
more than that.
I mean, you're going
to get together, right?
I don't think that we are.
But... you two are
supposed to be together.
Well, I thought so, too
but then she said
she'd marry you.
Come on, Ross, that
didn't mean anything.
She-she'd just had the baby.
She was all freaked out
about doing it alone.
Sh-She would have
said yes to anybody.
Yeah, th-that's what she said.
So?
So, I don't want
to be just anybody.
Wow.
You know what?
It's-it's better
this way anyway.
I mean, I don't know
what I was thinking
going down that road
again with us.
It's just much easier
if we're...
if we're just friends
who have a kid.
Really?
Yeah.
A-And you're okay with that?
Yes. I mean, it's what
we always planned.
And if you have a plan,
you should stick to it.
That's-that's why they
call them "plans." Hello?
I'm fine.
Hey, for what it's worth
with Rachel, I don't
think you'll ever be
just "anybody."
Hey, there you go.
"Thanks."
( Emma crying )
Oh, my God.
How long has she been crying?
About a week
and a half.
Well, it looks like
you guys got it under control
so I'm just going to go.
No? Really?
Misery really does love company?
All right.
Try holding her
a different way.
Look, you guys,
I'm doing the best I can.
Anyone else is welcome to try.
All right, I'll try.
Fine. Yes.
Okay.
Here you go.
Oh, gosh.
Shh...
( crying stops )
Nothing works with this child!
( crying starts again )
Oh, God, what am I going
to do, you guys?
I can't even comfort
my own baby.
I'm the worst mother ever.
No, you're just new at this.
You'll get better.
Think about
your first day at work.
That couldn't have been easy,
but you figured that out.
Yeah, I don't think
dressing provocatively
is going to help me here.
( sighs ):
Oh, God. Just please take her.
Okay, I'll take her.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
I have to go scream
into a pillow.
Bouncy...
♪ Bouncy baby ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby... ♪
( crying stops )
Have I gone deaf?
It worked.
♪ Oh, baby, baby, baby... ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
baby... ♪
You must be a fireball in bed.
( whispers ):
I can't believe it.
She's asleep.
I got her to go to sleep.
I have actual magical powers.
I can hear traffic and birds.
I can hear the voices
in my head again.
I'm kidding.
Oh, my God.
You got her to stop crying.
Yes, I did.
I'm Monica, Super Aunt.
You are the official
baby-crier-stopper.
Yes, I am.
You're never leaving
the apartment.
Say what?
That's your new job.
Day or night, she starts crying,
I need you here.
Oh, no, no, no.
All right,
well, uh, thankfully
you don't need me
at all, so...
Hey, Super Aunt, see you later.
Rachel, let's give it
six to eight months.
Okay, so listen,
I'm going to go lay down.
What?
You know, the book says
that whenever she's sleeping
I should be sleeping.
So... oh...
Hey.
Shh! We just got her
to go to sleep.
Oh, so th-there can't be
any yelling?
No.
We're moving to Tulsa.
What?!
Shh!
I can't... I can't hear.
Hey.
Where have you been?
( gasps )
What happened to you?
I had a little
thing with Joey.
If you think this is bad,
you should see him.
No, Ross, this is not good.
Please, we have to talk
about this Joey thing.
Please sit.
All right, you have got
to get over this Joey thing.
Okay, I never really wanted
to marry Joey, okay?
Okay.
You know what I really,
really want?
What, Rach?
I want to sleep.
I want to eat.
I want to take a shower.
I mean,
before she wakes up
and we got to do this
all over again.
Right.
I mean, 'cause I got
news for you, mister.
Emma? Not easy.
Well... that's
what I'm here for.
( Emma crying )
Want me to get that?
No, that's really okay.
Monica!
I got it, got it, got it.
You know, uh,
I've been thinking about this
and I got to tell you,
it's not my fault.
It's a natural instinct.
What are you guys
talking about?
Hey, okay, what would you do
if I did this?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org